window.albums = [
  { front: "bilder/1-front.webp", back: "bilder/1-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/2-front.webp", back: "bilder/2-back.webp", discs: 2 },
  { front: "bilder/3-front.webp", back: "bilder/3-back.webp", discs: 2 },
  { front: "bilder/4-front.webp", back: "bilder/4-back.webp", discs: 2 },
  { front: "bilder/5-front.webp", back: "bilder/5-back.webp", discs: 2 },
  { front: "bilder/6-front.webp", back: "bilder/6-back.webp", discs: 2 },
  { front: "bilder/7-front.webp", back: "bilder/7-back.webp", discs: 2 },
  { front: "bilder/8-front.webp", back: "bilder/8-back.webp", discs: 2 },
  { front: "bilder/9-front.webp", back: "bilder/9-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/10-front.webp", back: "bilder/10-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/11-front.webp", back : "bilder/11-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/12-front.webp", back: "bilder/12-back.webp", discs: 2 },
  { front: "bilder/13-front.webp", back: "bilder/13-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/14-front.webp", back: "bilder/14-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/15-front.webp", back: "bilder/15-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/16-front.webp", back: "bilder/16-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/17-front.webp", back: "bilder/17-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/18-front.webp", back: "bilder/18-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/19-front.webp", back: "bilder/19-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/21-front.webp", back: "bilder/21-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/22-front.webp", back: "bilder/22-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/23-front.webp", back: "bilder/23-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/24-front.webp", back: "bilder/24-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/25-front.webp", back: "bilder/25-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/26-front.webp", back: "bilder/26-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/27-front.webp", back: "bilder/27-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/28-front.webp", back: "bilder/28-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/29-front.webp", back: "bilder/29-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/30-front.webp", back: "bilder/30-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/31-front.webp", back: "bilder/31-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/32-front.webp", back: "bilder/32-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/33-front.webp", back: "bilder/33-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/34-front.webp", back: "bilder/34-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/35-front.webp", back: "bilder/35-back.webp", discs: 2 },
  { front: "bilder/36-front.webp", back: "bilder/36-back.webp", discs: 2 },
  { front: "bilder/37-front.webp", back: "bilder/37-back.webp", discs: 2 },
  { front: "bilder/38-front.webp", back: "bilder/38-back.webp", discs: 2 },
  { front: "bilder/39-front.webp", back: "bilder/39-back.webp", discs: 2 },
  { front: "bilder/40-front.webp", back: "bilder/40-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/41-front.webp", back: "bilder/41-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/42-front.webp", back: "bilder/42-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/43-front.webp", back: "bilder/43-back.webp", discs: 2 },
  { front: "bilder/44-front.webp", back: "bilder/44-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/45-front.webp", back: "bilder/45-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/46-front.webp", back: "bilder/46-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/47-front.webp", back: "bilder/47-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/48-front.webp", back: "bilder/48-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/49-front.webp", back: "bilder/49-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/50-front.webp", back: "bilder/50-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/51-front.webp", back: "bilder/51-back.webp", discs: 2 },
  { front: "bilder/52-front.webp", back: "bilder/52-back.webp", discs: 2 },
  { front: "bilder/53-front.webp", back: "bilder/53-back.webp", discs: 2 },
  { front: "bilder/54-front.webp", back: "bilder/54-back.webp", discs: 2 },
  { front: "bilder/55-front.webp", back: "bilder/55-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/56-front.webp", back: "bilder/56-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/57-front.webp", back: "bilder/57-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/58-front.webp", back: "bilder/58-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/59-front.webp", back: "bilder/59-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/60-front.webp", back: "bilder/60-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/61-front.webp", back: "bilder/61-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/62-front.webp", back: "bilder/62-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/63-front.webp", back: "bilder/63-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/64-front.webp", back: "bilder/64-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/65-front.webp", back: "bilder/65-back.webp", discs: 2 },
  { front: "bilder/66-front.webp", back: "bilder/66-back.webp", discs: 2 },
  { front: "bilder/67-front.webp", back: "bilder/67-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/68-front.webp", back: "bilder/68-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/69-front.webp", back: "bilder/69-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/70-front.webp", back: "bilder/70-back.webp", discs: 2 },
  { front: "bilder/71-front.webp", back: "bilder/71-back.webp", discs: 2 },
  { front: "bilder/72-front.webp", back: "bilder/72-back.webp", discs: 1 },
  { front: "bilder/73-front.webp", back: "bilder/73-back.webp", discs: 2 },
  { front: "bilder/74-front.webp", back: "bilder/74-back.webp", discs: 1 },
];